You know, I'm in the middle of recording this song, but I, why do y'all keep saying this?
Yet the U.S. and U.K. media continue to portray Iran as a threat to the region.
You know why they're doing that.
You know that the U.S. and the U.K. media are controlled by Zionists.
You know that the Zionists are the controlling, are controlling the, you see how irritated
they keep me talking?
You know that they're controlling the central banks, et cetera.
Why do we keep doing this thing where we just say like half the thing?
Why?
Why do we do it?
Why are we, why are we, why is it, why are we still doing this?
Matthew, like, come on.
Like, we know why the media is doing that.
We know who the media is.
We know what they are.
So every time that we say this, it just sounds like incredulity.
And I don't understand that because we know what the answer is.
And no, we're not living in Orwellian times.
The whole time has been Orwellian.
The times that, this type of thing is the same as watching majority report talk about
Democrats not showing up and not being about it like they're expecting it to be any different.
I just, can we cut it out?
It's just, let me get back to recording this song.
We'll see you next time.